<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/aggregator/rss.xml"/>
    <title>News</title>
    <link>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/aggregator</link>
    <description>Site News</description>

    <language>en</language>
    <copyright></copyright>
    <generator>Plone</generator>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 470.4B Chg 2 (MinChg), Safeguards and Security Program</title>
      <description>The order establishes responsibilities and program planning and management requirements for the Safeguards and Security Program. Supersedes DOE O 470.4B Chg 1.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 09:59:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0470.4B-chg2-minchg-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE P 485.1, Foreign Engagements with DOE National Laboratories</title>
      <description>The Department is committed to making DOE National Laboratories available to non-DOE entities, including foreign entities, as long as such work is consistent with or complementary to the missions of DOE and the laboratory to which the work is to be assigned, and does not impede the laboratory's ability to successfully accomplish its DOE missions.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 15:04:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0485.1-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE N 251.118, Cancellation of Directives</title>
      <description>Cancellation of DOE O 580.1A, Department of Energy Personal Property Management Program, dated 10-22-12.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 14:05:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0251.118-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 142.3A Chg 1 (MinChg), Unclassified Foreign Visits and Assignments Program</title>
      <description>The order defines a program for unclassified foreign national access to DOE sites, information, technologies, and equipment. Supersedes DOE O 142.3A</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 14:04:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0142.3a-chg1-mingchg-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 541.1C, Appointment of Contracting Officers and Contracting Officer Representatives</title>
      <description>To establish procedures governing the selection, appointment, and termination of all components of Department of Energy (DOE), including National Nuclear Security Administration contracting officers (COs) by ensuring federal staff are developed appropriately, in accordance with the Office of Federal Procurement Policy (OFPP) memorandum on May 7, 2014, entitled “Revisions to the Federal Acquisition Certification in Contracting (FAC-C).” Supersedes DOE O 541.1B, dated 4-21-2004.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 11:09:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0541.1c-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 450.2 Chg 1 (MinChg), Integrated Safety Management</title>
      <description>To ensure that the Department of Energy (DOE), including the National Nuclear Security Administration (NNSA), systematically integrates safety into management and work practices at all levels, so that missions are accomplished efficiently while protecting the workers, the public, and the environment. Supersedes DOE O 450.2, dated 4-24-2011.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 10:58:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0450.2-Chg1-MinChg-New</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 426.1A, Federal Technical Capability Program</title>
      <description>To define requirements and responsibilities for meeting the Department of Energy (DOE) commitment to recruiting, deploying, developing, and retaining a technically competent workforce that will accomplish DOE missions in a safe and efficient manner through the Federal Technical Capability Program (FTCP). Supersedes DOE O 426.1.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 09:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0426.1a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 415.1 Chg 2 (MinChg), Information Technology Project Management</title>
      <description>The Order provides program and project management direction for the acquisition and management of IT projects, investments, and initiatives. These changes implement The Federal Information Technology Acquisition Reform Act (FITARA) Supersedes DOE O 415.1 Admin Chg 1.

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 16:30:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0415.1-Chg2-MinChg-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 200.1A Chg 1 (MinChg), Information Technology Management</title>
      <description>The Order identifies the objectives, components, and responsibilities for implementing processes to ensure the effective management of information and information systems within the Department. Supersedes DOE O 200.1A.

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 16:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0200.1a-chg1-minchg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOE O 251.1D, Departmental Directives Program</title>
      <description>The Order establishes directives as the primary means to set, communicate, and institutionalize policies, requirements, responsibilities, and procedures for Departmental elements and contractors. Supersedes DOE O 251.1C.

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 09:40:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0251.001D-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOE O 232.2A, Occurrence Reporting and Processing of Operations Information</title>
      <description>The order promotes organizational learning consistent with DOE’s Integrated Safety Management System goal of enhancing mission safety, and sharing effective practices to support continuous improvement and adaptation to change. Supersedes DOE O 232.2 Admin Chg 1.

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 09:39:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0232.2a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE P 411.2A, DOE Scientific Integrity Policy</title>
      <description>The policy is intended to enhance our culture by establishing a unified framework for scientific integrity. Supersedes DOE P 411.2.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 10:28:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/p411.2a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 411.2, Scientific Integrity</title>
      <description>This Order implements DOE P 411.2A to ensure a culture of scientific integrity and facilitate free flow of scientific and technical information. Does not cancel/supersede other directives</description>
      
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 10:26:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0411.2-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 483.1B, DOE Cooperative Research and Development Agreements</title>
      <description>The order establishes policy, requirements, and responsibilities for the oversight, management, and administration of Cooperative Research and Development Agreement (CRADA) activities at DOE facilities.</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 10:04:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0483.1b-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New - DOE O 326.1A, Confidential Financial Disclosure Reports (OGE 450)</title>
      <description>The directive establishes requirements and responsibilities for Departmental elements and employees regarding filing Confidential Financial Disclosure Reports (OGE Form 450) in accordance with the Ethics in Government Act of 1978, as amended. Supersedes DOE O 326.1.

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 11:43:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.directives.doe.gov/news/0326.01A-new</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>